Guide to the Jamie Whitbeck's ImageOut collection, 1993-2011
Whitbeck's, Jamie ImageOut collection
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Jamie Whitbeck's ImageOut collection, 1993-2011
7807
Whitbeck, Jamie
2.2 cubic ft.
Correspondence, printed materials, and newspapers.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Jamie Whitbeck's collection of ImageOut, the Rochester Lesbian and Gay Film and Video Festival related materials including notes, meeting minutes, correspondence, press releases, festival programs, newsletters, fund raising and promotional materials as well as newspapers and news clippings.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Jamie Whitbeck's collection of ImageOut, the Rochester Lesbian and Gay Film and Video Festival related materials including notes, meeting minutes, correspondence, press releases, festival programs, newsletters, fund raising and promotional materials as well as newspapers and news clippings.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Whitbeck, Jamie
Subjects:
Gay and lesbian film festivals -- New York (State) -- Rochester.; Homosexuality in motion pictures; Gays in popular culture
Places:
New York (State) -- Rochester
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
Gay Alliance of the Genesee Valley records
NOTES
Arrangement and description of the amie Whitbeck's ImageOut collection, #7807 made possible in part by a grant from the Documentary Heritage Program of the New York State Archives, a program of the State Education Department
CONTAINER LIST
- Rochester Lesbian and Gay Film and Video Festival 1, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Rochester Lesbian and Gay Film and Video Festival 2, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Rochester Lesbian and Gay Film and Video Festival 2, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Rochester Lesbian and Gay Film and Video Festival 3, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Rochester Lesbian and Gay Film and Video Festival 3, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Binder
- Rochester Lesbian and Gay Film and Video Festival 3, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- ImageOut - Rochester Lesbian and Gay Film and Video Festival 4, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- ImageOut - Rochester Lesbian and Gay Film and Video Festival 4, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- ImageOut - Rochester Lesbian and Gay Film and Video Festival 4, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- ImageOut - Rochester Lesbian and Gay Film and Video Festival 4, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Film Festival - Transition to independence, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- ImageOut - Rochester Lesbian and Gay Film and Video Festival 5, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- ImageOut Press Releases, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- ImageOut - Rochester Lesbian and Gay Film and Video Festival 5, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- ImageOut Publicity, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Press Coverage, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Publicity Archive, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- ImageOut - Rochester Lesbian and Gay Film and Video Festival 6, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Film Festival Stationary, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- ImageOut - Rochester Lesbian and Gay Film and Video Festival 7, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- ImageOut Corporate sponsorship, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- ImageOut, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  Newspapers
- ImageOut- Rochester Lesbian and Gay Film and Video Festival 8, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- ImageOut - Rochester Lesbian and Gay Film and Video Festival 8, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Pacesetter Campaign, 200-2001 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- ImageOut - Rochester Lesbian and Gay Film and Video Festival 9, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- ImageOut - Rochester Lesbian and Gay Film and Video Festival 9, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Tickets, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- ImageOut News and ImageOut TAKES, 2001-2010 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Newsletters
- ImageArt, 2000-2004 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- ImageOut - Rochester Lesbian and Gay Film and Video Festival 10, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Pacesetter Campaign, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- ImageOut - Rochester Lesbian and Gay Film and Video Festival 11, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Pacesetter Campaign, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- ImageOut - Rochester Lesbian and Gay Film and Video Festival 12, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- ImageOut - Rochester Lesbian and Gay Film and Video Festival 12, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- ImageOut - Tickets and Theatre Ops., 2005 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- ImageOut - Rochester Lesbian and Gay Film and Video Festival 13, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- ImageOut - Rochester Lesbian and Gay Film and Video Festival 14, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Posters, 1994, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  Hope for All the Children and GAGV Pride Parade 20th Anniversary
- ImageOut - Rochester Lesbian and Gay Film and Video Festival 15, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- ImageOut - Rochester Lesbian and Gay Film and Video Festival 16, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- ImageOutreach, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- ImageOutreach, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- ImageOut - Theatre Ops, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- ImageOut - Rochester Lesbian and Gay Film and Video Festival 17, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- ImageOutreach - Community Partners, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Rochester Lesbian and Gay Film and Video Festival Programs, 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- ImageOut Programs, 1998-2000 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- ImageOut Programs, 2001-2002, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- ImageOut Programs, 2005-2007 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- ImageOut Programs, 2009-2011 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Press Kits, 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Newspapers and news clippings, 1999-2004, 2009-2010 (Box 3)
  Rochester based newspapers